dailytech.com 2010-12-30

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy of DailyTech LLC

DailyTech LLC recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of you as a user of this Website. This Website does not collect Personal Information about you except for information that you voluntarily provide (for example: When you submit an email to us with comments about our web site, articles, posts or products and you do not specifically indicate that the information contained within is to be considered confidential or you provide answers to a voluntary readership survey.) We do set cookies from time to time to better gage our readership level. No Personal Information is gathered via these cookies. 

Personal Information is treated confidentially. We consider the following to be Personal Information: your name, address, phone number, date of birth, your e-mail address and data about the pages you visited on this Website.

**Legal Disclaimer**

All the information and contents posted on this Web Site are the property of DailyTech LLC, and are protected by U.S. and foreign copyright and trademark laws. By accessing this Web Site, you agree to the following terms and conditions. If you do not agree, you have no right to use this Web Site or its content. 

  1. This Web Site and its contents as well as content from publications using DailyTech LLC syndication services may not be copied or distributed in any manner without the prior written consent of DailyTech LLC. With the following exception: You may copy up to 10 words or paraphrase an article provided that you specifically and exclusively attribute the material to www.dailytech.com. 
  2. DailyTech LLC makes no representations or warranties with respect to this Web Site, its contents or the manuscript, which are provided for use "as is" and is without warranty of any kind. 
  3. Portions of this Web Site may publish reader’s comments and opinions. DailyTech LLC does not assume or have any responsibility or any liability for the reader’s comments or opinions 

If you have questions about our privacy or legal policies, Send an email to [privacy@dailytech.com](mailto:privacy@dailytech.com)

**Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

* * *

Most Popular ArticlesRumored iPad 2 to Ship in January  
December 23, 2010, 7:18 AM  
FCC Gives Internet Firms the Gift of Net Neutrality  
December 25, 2010, 3:20 PM  
Demand for Gasoline in U.S. is on Permanent Decline  
December 23, 2010, 11:16 AM  
W.T.F., What's Going On? CIA Wikileaks Panel Reveals Findings  
December 23, 2010, 9:20 AM  
HTC Hopes to Force "Sense" into Windows Phone 7  
December 24, 2010, 11:06 AM
